We've had a podcast guest not show up,
so we're going to make the most of that
hour,
and we're going to critique some of your
content.
Before we get into it, remember, guys,
if you want me to take a look at your
Instagram,
and you want me to have a look at your
sales process, use the link in
the description below
and I'll add it to the next video. Okay,
let's get into it.
First things first,
hate this profile picture.
Although it might impress other personal
trainers, most of the people that want to
hire you as a coach see this
and just think,
"Pleb." I want a coach that's going to
care about me, and when I see a guy who,
no offense, clearly just loves himself
more than anyone else, I mean, cool,
you found some down light and you got
shredded.
It just makes me feel like everything of
your brand is about you.
Now, for some of you
that may not be fully aware, our jobs
are to be self-servient
to literally everyone else but ourselves.
Our content should help other people.
It shouldn't be about helping ourself.
Our coaching program should help other
people, not help ourselves.
Even our businesses should be centric
around helping other people,
not ourselves.
So already you're off to a bad start with
that. Sixty-five posts.
Mate,
you've just not really done enough to
really know anything.
"Lose fat, build muscle."
That needs some work, mate.
Help you lose fat, build muscle?
Help myself lose fat, build muscle?
Lose fat, build muscle.
They're the two kind of changes.
Don't really say too much.
Ten years training. Wow, that's cool,
but don't care. Natural.
That's cool, don't care.
"DM coach for a one-" Mate, I cannot
stand this as a call to action.
The amount of people,
"DM me the word coach." How
about no? "For a one-to-one coaching,
book your free consult call." Look,
no one's going to be DMing you for
one-to-one coaching.
I bet no one has ever DM'd you for
Book your free consult call.
It's a sales call, mate.
Look, I hate this, to be perfectly honest.
I think your bio is aids.
And the fact that you can give me a
fitness consult, it's not.
It's a sales call.
We know it. You know it.
Everyone knows it.
Just call it a fucking sales call.
But better yet, the issue here is,
I don't know what it is you're selling me,
what
I get, why I need it,
how people have done with you before.
The landing page would've been such a
better option here, man.
Because with a landing page,
I can find out how expensive you are,
I can look at
client testimonials,
I can look at what I'm going to get.
There is such a big barrier.
It's like meeting someone on the dance
floor.
Your next objective should be to get their
number, should be then to text them for
a bit,
should be then to take them for dinner,
then to try and get in their pants.
This is just an absolute approach of,
here's a little bit of information,
now suck
my dick.
And just because one in 1,000 people might
do it, doesn't mean it works.
Now, when I get to your calendar,
I know what you're doing here.
Oh, how convenient
that he only has two slots available
every day. It's not because you're busy,
it's because you're trying to give the
illusion that you're busy. Now,
unless someone has those two slots,
they're just
not going to be able to book, which again,
is just not that good. Gilliam G.
Don't call yourself G. And that pic
is just not doing it, mate.
It's homoerotic. I look at that pic
and I think you've got your dick in your
hand.
This is like when people went on Chat
Roulette, and they
were quite clearly having
a wank under the table. That
is the face that they would pull.
So for me, so far, it's a one out of 10.
Now, even when I get to your profile here.
Come on, bro.
This does not scream to me,
"I help people." This screams to me,
"I love
myself." And you should love yourself,
self-care and all that.
But all I'm seeing here is narcissism,
not coaching.
And if you're trying to be an aspiring
fitness model,
and you want to get Gymshark
to sign you, that's cool. But until then,
you need to start making content
that's going to benefit other people,
because once you help people enough times,
there's something called the law of
reciprocity.
They go, "My God,
I need to hire this person." I can assume
this is why you're
putting your physique up for critique.
But this is just gay. All right,
moving on.
Oh, you're not allowed to use that word.
I meant it as in the use of happy.
Okay, moving up one. The Bake House.
God,
hopefully this won't be a fitness page.
I like this. The Bake House Wirral.
Sorry about the shitty Wi-Fi.
Straight away, I kind of know what it is.
I bet it's a bake house. Look at this,
20,000 followers already.
I can tell you exactly why that is.
Two and a half thousand posts,
getting at it,
getting busy. That's what I like to see.
Success leaves clues.
That's what people say. My God,
is this on fucking dial-up, Declan?
Are we on AOL? Fucking 300
kilobytes a second. See, this is nice.
Three locations, one phone number.
I like it.
I would like probably some kind of call to
action up there. Let's have a look.
See,
this is pretty promising because you're
getting some pretty strong views on
some of your stuff. 28K here, 18K here.
And there's a pretty good idea that
if you can just celebrate nice food.
Now, people often wonder why recipes
and cooking does so well.
I like to remind people,
the UK at the moment,
maybe 16% of people have a gym
membership. But everyone eats. So
if you're in the food niche or the
drink niche, everyone eats and drinks.
Not everyone goes to the gym.
So when you do a recipe video versus a
bicep curl, you're going to get more
interest because, like I say,
everyone eats.
What I'm going to do
is I'm going to start loading the next
Instagram page because
we're on fucking AOL dial-up here, Declan.
Might even have to load the fucking next
two. Oh, yeah. Horse puss. Come on.
Fucking Wi-Fi's kind of picked up a bit
now.
Do you reckon the lads next door have
stopped looking at goat porn?
Literally, the Wi-Fi's back.
They're off the goat porn.
What do you mean, what the fuck
is goat porn?
Quite clearly and evident, goat porn
is porn of goats. See, look at this.
"The new Hail Caesar is flirting with you,
Bake House Wirral." I kind of like this
because there's a story to this.
You could just look at this as like a
sandwich
being made,
but they're showing you how it begins.
It's kind of inspiring people to do their
own. I like it.
"Are you treating your weekend to a Bake
House?" Hmm.
Okay,
so showing off seems to do quite well.
Sixty-seven likes is still good because,
again, it can seem counterintuitive, but
someone in the local area might just
follow their local bake house.
But then seeing something like this,
they go, "Do you know what?
It's my nan's birthday next week.
I'm going to go down that bake house
and order a
little cake." And there
are so many bake houses out there probably
just not
showcasing their food, and this
is just going to be the thing
that separates
people. And imagine
if they've got 10 competitors within 10
kilometers, just being
active on social media just separates you
from the rest. I kind of like this.
I feel like maybe there should be an offer
in your call to
action, like best cake you've ever had
or your money back, and then your
locations.
Just something with a call to action.
But this is really good.
Now, if I was you, because I'm mental,
you've got this
cult-like following, 20,000 people,
I would love for you to showcase
maybe to tell people how they could cook
some of this stuff from home.
So never to the same standard of you,
but there should be maybe a call to action
here where it's like, "Look,
if you want to learn how to create this,
comment the
word cake or biscuit or sandwich.
I'm going to send you detailed
instruction.
You can make bakery quality food from
home." Then
you're just going to collect emails from
it, because out of this 20,000.
My golden rule is that 20% of people
that follow you should have their emails.
Then for those 20% of people,
you could run campaigns like ordering
birthday cakes,
like ordering work events, bespoke cakes,
things like that.
If it was my mate's birthday
and I could get a cake with his face on
it, I'd spend
a couple of hundred quid on that.
So it'd be quite cool to maybe get some
data from
this. You could also run a bake club.
You could be online.
You could just have these three locations.
Then imagine if you had a couple of
hundred people paying you £5.99 a month,
and
every week they just get some kind of the
Great British Bake Off.
And you could even call it like the Bake
House Bake Off, and every single person
that bakes the best each week gets a
coupon for 50% off a birthday cake.
Whatever it is.
There's a digital product
that can definitely be added to this.
I like this. Already you're crushing it.
I just feel like maybe there could be
something else so
that I don't know where any
of these places are, but if I
was living in Berkshire,
I might follow you, see your
content, then I might go,
"Do you know what?
I am going to take
that digital download asset to learn how
to bake." Okay.
Informed Rider Coaching. I like
that because it tells me what it is.
However, I feel like this
is your brand name,
but I think you should be Katie Hancox.
Because if I'm learning amazing things
about riding, I'm learning it from
Katie Hancox,
not from Informed Rider Coaching.
If you send me an invoice,
that can be on it.
But ultimately, if people
are going to share your profile with other
people,
they're going to go, "Oh,
do you follow Katie Hancox?" Remember,
you don't follow
Modern Wisdom,
you follow Chris Williamson.
You don't follow Diary of a CEO,
you follow Steven Bartlett.
You don't follow Nutonic,
but you might do,
but you probably follow me or Chris.
So although I don't mind this,
I just think that this handle should try
to
be you, because you're currently under,
you're hiding under it.
It should be better. Equestrian coach,
educator, love that.
This post to follower ratio probably means
we haven't quite hit it yet, but that's
okay. This above the fold stuff here,
if you do want people
to click,
I would maybe shorten this just so
that it's visible.
Maybe less information there. Oh,
I do like the fact we have a pricing plans
list. We'll get to that in a second.
Now let's have a look here.
These thumbnails, they're okay,
but I sometimes feel like people put too
much
effort into these compared to other stuff.
But let's have a little look.
We're always like, is it me?
Am I the drama or is it-
Unless you're doing it on YouTube, this
is just in the wrong format.
And when people are swiping on reels
and they get to that, they're just
going to think this
was kind of just put on there.
Just things that you struggle with being
in equestrian.
So they work off person. Do your actions
meet your narrative? In other-
Could probably do need to do a little bit
of work on the hooks here.
I can see you've already started to go
with it.
What I would say is because you're quite
small, you need to kind of push yourself
out there.
One thing I tell to people to do
is try using three
words to establish your hook. Now,
three words can be punchy.
It could be like, "This is wrong.
Don't do this. Try doing this.
This is a mistake." Whatever it is,
even though that's more than three words.
So then a three-word hook can really get
yourself across in front of people a
little bit sooner. Like I say,
this format is probably not
ideal.
You're getting some good likes though
here, so look.
The only issue is if I go through your
content, I'm not really honing in on the
problems that you're solving.
So I would love for you to create like a
common enemy
with horse riding, whether it is
that people are being taught to ride wrong
or
there's kind of like a common theme about
riding that's wrong.
But when I look at this,
I don't see what that is.
I would love for you to have a specific
niche of people that you help.
Just a little bit vague, but okay.
Here we have a landing page
and a squeeze page
trying to do the same thing.
What I mean by this is
when we take people away from
Instagram,
we either want to send them to a squeeze
page where the objective is to
get their email address,
or we want to send them to a landing page
where the
objective is to sell.
I don't like blurring the lines between
the two.
I just feel like it's not great.
So this is all good, but this should be a
squeeze page,
should be connected to a lead magnet,
not just a pop-up when we land
here. Now again,
you go straight to pricing.
I have a little flow
that I like on landing pages.
It goes like this.
What it is, what I get, why I need it,
why I trust you, how
to pay. So the first three
are pretty straightforward,
but the why to trust you can
be testimonials or a money-back guarantee.
And then when I'm presented with pricing,
I look at this and I go, "Well, if it's
not all I thought it was,
I can get my money back."
88 every month, 48 every month,
129 six-week challenge.
This is okay,
but we're just going straight into
pricing.
Informed Equestrian membership choices.
We could have just told me what it was,
and then one thing that's going to be a
key
player on this would be a VSL, which
is a video sales letter.
Which is a video of you just saying, "Hey,
it's Katie." Was it?
"Hi, it's Katie." Oh, here they are.
"Welcome to Informed Rider Coaching.
Basically, there are three tiers below.
Let me talk you through them very quickly,
and at the end I'm going to give you a
guarantee which makes you feel safe from
the purchase." Because yeah, everything
kind of is in a bit of the wrong order
there.
Also, these fonts
are very difficult to read.
So going black on dark green
is just a no-no.
I do like the contrast between the others,
but you'd be surprised how people can
improve their conversions just by making
text easier to read.
Save my spot. Buy.
Quite a lot going on here.
But again,
if you had pages made specifically for
different things, this is also a
website versus a landing page.
I just don't particularly like having
loads of
different things to click on
when I'm in here. Log in.
Whoa, is this a membership website?
But anyway. Okay.
Noah Bailey Fitness.
I'm getting vibes of the fucking last guy.
Again, you doing a tricep pose in the
mirror. No one's going, "Fucking hell.
Can't wait to hire this guy." You know?
"Fuck, bro, this guy's tricep's so good.
I've got to join this program." Again,
you're looking at yourself in the
reflection. You're admiring.
You've gone to someone, "Hey, bro,
can you get a
picture of this pump,
please?" Very self-centered.
Very self-centric.
Yeah, so classic name, fitness, cool.
Online coach and PT, cool.
Thirty-eight posts.
Mate, I've done more than
that this week quite literally.
You've not done that much. 191 followers.
That's generous for a profile picture like
that.
"I help busy people who feel stuck in
their gym journey." Who
isn't busy? How many people are like, "Oh,
I wish I was busier"?
And who feels stuck in their gym journey?
What is a gym journey?
What is the outcome I want?
Gain muscle and lose fat. Oh, fuck me.
I haven't heard that before.
It's just It's quite basic. If you
were to say, imagine this, right?
I'm a builder,
you're hiring me as a builder,
and they go, "James, what do you
specialize in?" "I do everything." "All
right. Okay." "Yeah, everything.
Driveways, roofing, bathrooms, anything.
I do it all." "Okay, cool.
Sounds pretty good." Then another builder
comes past.
"What do you do?" "Look, mate,
I do bathrooms and kitchens. That's it.
If you need your driveway done,
see someone else.
If you need your roof done,
I know a couple of people.
But bathrooms and kitchens
are where I specialize.
I can actually show you a deck.
I've transformed many bathrooms
and kitchens.
Anywhere there's plumbing,
or you might want to get some new tiles in
there, it's
what I've done for 20 years.
And like I say,
I've got connections in other
industries, but if it's a kitchen
or bathroom,
that's really what I specialize in."
Now, I'm not saying I'm broad,
where I only do certain levels of things,
but I now
seem more believable, for a start.
The fact I would've sent you somewhere
else to get roofing done is a start.
Now,
you're either going to be a hypertrophy
coach or you're going to be a fat loss
coach. The reality is most people
when they lose fat think they've gained a
bit of
muscle anyway, but this just says,
"I want to help absolutely
everyone." And by that,
no one's really going to vibe.
Qualified PT, no one cares,
and online coach, also, no one
cares. Apply for one-to-one coaching.
Mate, sorry to break this to you,
but you're not a fucking Sora House
membership.
People aren't going to apply.
You're going to take anyone.
You've got fucking 190 followers,
so don't make it apply.
The reason you've said apply,
I guarantee we're going to go to some
fucking
Typeform or bullshit here, aren't we?
Okay. All right. I underestimated you.
We have got a landing page.
This branding can go.
Coaching to help you make sustainable
long-term changes to your health and
fitness. Bit boring, I'll say that.
This font, whoever signed
that off can die.
Do you want to make changes to your health
and fitness but constantly feel...
This gives me a headache reading it, mate.
Come on.
Times New Roman would've been better than
this.
Maybe a little bit of Trebuchet Bold,
but this is awful.
Everyone has different goals
and lifestyles. Some people... Okay.
We can help you get on the right track.
We?
Is it you singular or we? Who else is we?
Double gun pose on a mountain.
So far, mate, this ain't looking good.
I've got a tricep flex, double gun pose.
Add them together, equates cunt. So,
even if you were to just stand there
with your hands by your side,
I'd like you 25% more.
Your coaching,
one-to-one online coaching services.
Personal training sessions. Okay.
Everlast Gym Cheltenham.
Cheltenham, Gloucestershire.
Used to go there. Moo Moo's.
Vodka Revs, Cheltenham,
probably the best one in the planet.
Anyway,
don't promote your personal training here,
because let's say you do fix
this, which needs a bit of work.
When you do it,
the chances of someone being close
enough to come train in Cheltenham,
just unlikely.
So get rid of that, because
if you make good enough content,
people will come to
you from in-persons.
One-to-one online coaching.
One week free trial, no obligations. Cool.
Bespoke training, tailored macro tracking,
fortnightly
review calls. People don't want them,
by the way,
any fitness coach watching this.
Check-ins, they hate them.
They don't want to do them.
People hate check-ins.
I can't believe it's 2026,
people just finding this out.
Exclusive educational content.
£120 per month. What am I looking at?
£30 a week. Yeah, it's all right.
Progress guarantee.
If you complete one month of coaching
and you've made no meaningful progress,
I'll
refund you in full. Full details and T&C.
Actually,
let's go have a little look at the T&C.
Where is that little T&C?
Look at that. Man's got terms
and conditions.
Cor, fuck me, this text
is giving me a fucking headache.
You didn't do this.
This is ChatGPT. It is. I know it is.
Where's that money-back guarantee?
Payment. Refunds. Refunds
are not available for any services
already provided or for cancellations
outside of the progress guarantee outlined
in
Section 6. Let's go to Section 6,
shall we? Okay. Free trial.
Cor, this fucking text, mate. Okay.
Attend and complete all scheduled
sessions, check-ins,
and agreed activities.
Communicate openly
and honestly throughout the program.
What you're doing here
is you're actually giving yourself ways to
not refund
people.
I can see this a million miles away.
You're going to go, "Oh, actually,
if you check Section 6, the progress
guarantee,
you actually didn't attend a call on
Tuesday the 6th, which means
you're not getting a refund." Listen,
mate. Get rid of all this fucking shit.
If someone wants their money back,
just give it to them.
Because what you do not want
is someone to fucking hate you.
And if your coaching is shit for
that person, which it might always be,
and you do
not refund them,
they will go out of their way to tell
people how shit you are.
They're going to tank your fucking
reviews.
They're going to make your life hell.
So take it from me, even
if someone doesn't qualify for a refund,
just give them a
fucking refund. Mate,
some cunt yesterday messaged me going,
"There was a bit of
rust on the new tonic can." Now,
it wasn't rust.
It's made out of fucking aluminum.
It's only a few weeks old.
But I said, "Yep, cool.
I'll refund you the can." There
was nothing wrong with that
can,
but I did it because I don't want some
fucking cunt from the middle of nowhere
chatting shit about my product.
Do you know what I mean?
For £2.75, you can have it.
I only sent him £2.50 to make up for it.
But anyway,
that is just a load of bollocks.
So just from me to you,
just get rid of that. Yeah. This font,
got to go.
Hate it. Meet your coach.
You know this bit here,
no one gives a fuck.
I'm just saying this in the nicest way
possible.
No one cares about my qualifications,
where I went to uni, where I did a BTEC,
what
grades I got.
Do you know what they care about?
Themselves.
That's all people care about.
And this picture just goes to show
that you think
that your tricep is more important than
your client,
and that's just not the way it
is.
We're going to review your content
quickly. Okay.
You see the issue here, brother.
You tensing a mirror.
I'm sorry to tell you this, bro,
but you are not him.
Oh, no,
I think I've just double liked your post.
Can't undo that now. Anyway.
I'm very excited to share, okay, cool,
my sports and fitness journey.
Some people care here, but I don't.
Why you should be doing unilateral
training.
Bro, come on. Imagine I
was hiring a videographer, Declan.
First day at work, he comes in,
gets his top off.
I go, "What are you doing,
mate?" "Training my muscles." "Fine.
I just want you to be good at your job."
"Yeah, but I got muscles." "Don't care."
You might be doing too much in the gym.
Why don't you just talk into the camera?
Tips to get more protein in your diet.
Don't neglect breakfast. Fucking hell,
mate.
Get this guy a fucking Nobel Prize.
Why weight loss medications don't actually
work. Sorry? Let's listen to this.
The solution to your weight problems.
And first of all,
I completely understand why people would
go for these.
They're a quick solution, less work,
but let me explain why.
In short, what they pretty much do
is trick your brain into thinking
that it's too
full and not hungry. Eventually-
Good to see you sang, mate, for just this.
I get it,
you're probably threatened by weight loss
medications thinking they're
going to put you out of business.
But has it ever occurred to you that
if quite
literally 10, 15,
20,000 fat people in Cheltenham
and Gloucester use
these GLP-1 medications and lose 20,
30 kilograms, their biggest concerns are
offsetting or bone density
and muscle loss.
And do you know where the best places to
offset those are? In the gym.
The Everlast gym that you work in.
By telling people not to take these
medications,
you keep them fat and out of the gym.
But if you told them to take these
medications, they come in.
They're going to come in to you as a
client and go, "Hey, can you help
me, not with my diet, not with my eating,
not with anything, just to
train and train hard
and preserve muscle?" These make your job
easier, bro, and
they give you way more people to work
with.
So you saying it's a shortcut, you
are quite literally making your life
so much harder. If you
were to embrace these
and not judge people for them, people
would come to you and go,
"Loved your video online about GLP-1s.
Where can I start?
This is what I'm trying to do." How do I
know?
Because I'm getting hundreds
and hundreds of clients enjoying my GLP-1
videos and
use me as a coach because they know
they're not going to get judged
or stigmatized.
I get it. I thought this at the beginning,
then I had a bit of a harsh reality
check. This is a great stance
if you hate money.
If you hate money, keep that stance.
I'm just going to throw this out.
I don't want to watch you train, bro.
All right.
"Your physique is a physical manifestation
of your mind." Yeah.
A bit self-centered, all this, mate.
Not once have you held a product
or spoken about something,
fat burners, AG1, bands, equipment.
This looks to me like a page about you,
not about them.
So keep your top on,
put your fucking muscles away.
Stop all of this shit.
If you went on a mission for the next 300
posts to just try and help
people,
you might actually have some people
applying for your coaching.
And don't say apply for coaching.
Just say, get coaching, buy coaching,
check out what I do, work with me.
There are ways that
are going to be so much
better than that. And remember, mate,
I can sound like I'm being a bit harsh
sometimes,
but if I really wanted to be a prick,
I'd say, "Yeah, looks good." It
doesn't. Not at all. And like I say,
keep doing that if you hate money.
Don't even know what we're looking at
here. Skipping this one.
What the fuck is that? Let's try this one.
This is going to be the last one.
Last one we're getting into. Right.
Georges Burr. Oh, fuck me.
156,000 followers.
This one could be interesting.
Doesn't follow me.
Hater. Straight away. Hater.
It's only the business page, to be fair.
770 posts, 156. Good ratios,
I'll give you that.
GB Fitness Health. Hello, booked by Hello,
coaching programs.
What have we got here?
Appeal to authority.
Playing rugby at a high level.
Like to see it.
You know why I feel like that.
Let's have a look at this. 15, 76, 19.
I would say we have had some kind of
rebrand here.
Actually,
I think I've seen your page before.
Now, let's try and, George Burr.
Found you. Tracked you down.
You think you can escape me, brother?
I'm going to dox you in front of everyone.
"Married at First Sight." Here we go,
brother. Here we go.
Fucking found you, brother.
I knew I could smell it.
I could smell it. Them ratios
were a bit mad.
Very interesting. Very interesting.
Let's get off the site.
It makes me feel sick. Okay,
so what we've got here
is what we call the pivot.
We've got the absolute pivot going on.
Because I remember you popping off in the
Discord before. Right.
It's going to be difficult because this
isn't what people followed you for,
but we're getting some good amount of
engagement.
So I suppose the question here
is whether or not you use the fitness
account or
this one.
These ain't going to work for a start,
I'll tell you that.
They're not real tweets.
They don't look like real tweets.
They worked in 2019, but not anymore,
I'm afraid, brother.
And these should be your last resort.
Yeah.
This page I don't think is doing enough,
to be
perfectly honest.
I would probably lean into the last one a
little bit more.
The one thing I'm not seeing,
these hashtags got to go.
That's 100 weeks, I'll let you off.
I'm not seeing any call to actions.
We need to get some chatbot.
Let's get rid of these hashtags.
Even the CEO of Instagram was like,
"They don't work." I would love to see you
not
getting into all these memes and stuff.
You're just engagement baiting here.
I would love,
whatever influencer hat you have on has
got to go.
Your job now is to give people information
they can use to transform their life.
See, like this,
instead of being on a leg press
and putting this, just write a
fucking article, mate.
You know what I mean?
Write a LinkedIn post.
Post it on Twitter.
Because there's no you looking around the
gym doing a leg press
with this.
I get you've got a bit of engagement,
but I just don't get it.
Don't get it.
Why not just fucking get a WeGoV box,
hold it, take a picture of
yourself,
and do a proper article about it?
Or if this is your stance,
fucking say it to camera.
It's such a good hook.
This is Manjaru,
and this pen here proved to the world
that the body positivity
movement was a lie.
Then you could explain.
Then if that's fucking enough of a talking
point, make it a YouTube video.
If you add this as a talking point
and you went, "James, how
is the worst way I
could get this across to someone?" I'd go,
record yourself doing a leg press. Yeah.
Just look around the gym. Yeah.
Put some text over it. Fantastic.
Going to go home and do that now.
Wasted opportunity. Come on, bro.
No, no, no.
I don't care about your miso chicken
rice bowl, mate.
No one woke up today wanting a rice bowl.
How are you, James? I'm depressed.
I need help. Why?
Is it because you're fat? No. Unfit? No.
Weak? No.
Just could do with a little peanut miso
chicken bowl.
No one's woken up today going,
"That's great." These 39 likes
are sympathy likes.
Oh, there he is.
Guy from "Married at First Sight." He's
trying. Double tap.
That's it. That is it. Stop this.
None of these educational posts
are going to
change my life. I love doing this, right?
Just quickly.
I'm going to take you over to,
I pretty much suck off this guy at this
point.
You heard of Ben Yangs? Yeah.
Fucking weapon, mate.
Every video he does is with actually like,
should you lean whilst doing a row?
So many people have stopped to this
and gone, "Oh, do you know what?
I actually don't know
if I should lean." Or some people,
such as myself, lean
without even really knowing the
difference.
I just know there's a difference.
Here comes the anatomy lesson,
and where he's talking to me,
not like I'm an idiot,
but he's also just helping me understand.
After watching this video,
I now know more.
He's not massively jacked, no offense,
Ben Yangs.
He's just, everything he does
is about helping me.
Oh, and a call to action lead magnet.
Awkward getting cable down on flies.
Twisting. How much does
that rotation actually affect it?
Loads of discourse,
loads of call to actions,
loads of anatomy lessons.
Every one of these videos has the impact
and potential to change my
fucking life. So
when you're there measuring out a bowl of
cereal or pretending to
cry,
I hope you appreciate why I think it's
pathetic.
So every single video
is with people in mind,
and that's why he's getting so
much engagement.
And out of all this engagement,
he's going to be getting loads of
people on his email list.
And with all the people on his email list,
he's going to
be firing them offers.
And out of people he's firing the offers
to, people are
going to buy. And that is why he's got
5,000 fucking members in his school.
It's free, granted, but I bet
when you're in there,
that man's...
And it all starts from the top,
making good content.
So hopefully no feelings
are hurt from that, but success
leaves clues. A lot of you
are too self-obsessed.
You care about yourself.
You pretend it's too much in the fucking
mirror.
You don't actually have any connection
or resonance with your clients, and if you
only went on a mission to help other
people, they would help you back by buying
your shit. So if you hate money,
keep doing what you're doing.
But if you love money,
try doing something different.
If you want me to take a look at your
profile,
there's a link in the description.
And you should do it because you might be
worried that I'm going to rip you a new
one, but isn't that the best thing
that could happen to you? All right.
If you enjoyed this video,
check out this one here because YouTube
reckons you'll
enjoy it.
And if you don't want to watch that one,
well, you can fuck off